Deep Sea 3D is a documentary film directed by Howard Hall.
Sea life in a whole new way.
Deep Sea 3D, an underwater adventure from the filmmakers behind the successful IMAX® 3D
film Into the Deep, transports audiences deep below the ocean surface.
Through the magic of IMAX®; and IMAX 3D, moviegoers will swim with some of the planets most
unique, dangerous and colorful creatures, and understand this inspiring underworld.
Narrator (voice), played by Kate Winslet.
Deep Sea 3D is a 3D IMAX documentary film about sea life.
The documentary is directed by Howard Hall who has also directed other
undersea films such as Into the Deep and Island of the Sharks.
The film is narrated by Johnny Depp and Kate Winslet.
It also features music by Danny Elfman.
The film is 40 minutes long.
The film shows various sea animals, such as jellyfish,
octopuses, and turtles as well as coral reef life.
The film explores themes of octopus, underwater, sea turtle, shrimp, manta ray.
The tone is uplifting and thought_provoking.